Master.
Just take me with you.
I am sticking with you.
Didn't I tell you last night?
Stop following me.
Master.
I promise.
I absolutely won't bother you.
Just let me serve by your side.
Move.
Master.
I...
Why are you still following me?
Master.
This road was built by the government.
You go your way.
I'll go mine.
How is that following you?
Sir,
are you eating or staying the night?
Bring a pot of good wine.
And heat up some vegetables and dried meat.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Kid,
go beg somewhere else.
Get lost.
Who said I'm a beggar?
You.
Bring me your best wine
and meat.
Do you have money?
Stop pretending.
Hurry up and get lost.
Don't delay my business.
I have plenty of money.
I failed to recognize your greatness.
Forgive my neglect.
The best wine and meat will be served right away.
Coming right up. Please wait.
Go away.
Just a moment.
Drink.
Can I help you?
What are you doing?
Where did these things
come from?
They're mine.
Yours?
You're so young.
Where did you get so much gold and silver?
My family gave it to me.
From your family?
Look at your outfit.
Do you look like you are from a wealthy family?
Recently, wealthy merchants in town were robbed.
Could it be
that you did it?
No, it wasn't me.
Still denying it?
Confiscate the gold and silver.
Escort him back to the government office.
It really wasn't me.
No, no, no.
Let me go!
Sir, it really wasn't me.
Move!
Who's blocking the way?
It is I,
Gesang.
What proof do you have
that this boy's gold and silver
are stolen?
Coming to this wilderness
with so much gold and silver.
If it isn't stolen,
where did it come from?
Besides,
even if there's a mistake,
we will take him back to the office
and find out through interrogation.
You have no right
to point fingers here.
Get lost!
Or you'll be charged with obstructing official duties.
Take him back to the yamen.
I'm afraid you corrupt officials
want to embezzle these gold and silver.
Then you'll find a place
to bury this young man,
without anybody
knowing.
How dare you!
How dare you slander an imperial official?
Men, arrest her!
Be careful!
I'll deal with you first.
Master.
Today,
there are really a lot of people seeking death.
Attack!
Yes.
Divine Taiji,
Heaven and Earth align,
Energy of the Eight Wastelands,
Yin and Yang manifest.
Xun position.
This guy actually knows sorcery.
Just you wait.
When I return to report to the Sitian Tower,
I will have all of you arrested.
Retreat.
Where did this gold and silver come from?
I went to Leilong's stronghold last night
and found a lot of treasure.
I left some
for the villagers.
And the rest
I kept for myself.
Foolish!
If anyone had stayed behind in the mountain,
you would definitely be dead.
There was no one there.
It seems
Leilong took them all down the mountain.
These treasures
must have been stolen by them.
They should be handed over to the authorities,
who will return them to the people following procedures.
Listen.
I'll go with you to the county office
to return these treasures,
so you won't get a bounty on your head.
What?
You're not going?
I'll go.
I will do as you say, Master.
But let me make this clear first.
After returning the property,
you must not follow me anymore.
Otherwise,
I won't go easy on you.
Why are you following me?
Master.
I...
I am Gesang.
You are so skilled.
What sect are you from?
None of your business.
I know what you are.
You were in danger just now,
but you still restrained yourself.
It shows you are not evil.
I will spare your life for now.
Don't follow me anymore.
He's just like that.
Sister Gesang.
I am Feilu.
Thank you.
By the way,
if you want someone to look after you,
just follow us secretly.
That master is very powerful.
He is an immortal.
An immortal?
The way he is,
how does he look like an immortal?
Let's go.
Coming.
Last night,
I felt immortal power nearby through the ley lines.
I couldn't be wrong.
Did I really meet one?
Sanshan Sect.
A Golden Immortal.
Master.
You hunted this?
I learned to hunt with the villagers since I was a kid.
They all praised my steady aim.
Not bad.
You're too kind, Master.
I'll go find some leaves.
We can use them as a mattress tonight.
Sister Gesang.
For me?
Yeah.
I couldn't just watch you go hungry.
Besides,
I owe you one.
Thanks.
Thank you.
You said
he is an immortal.
Have you seen him transform into an immortal?
Sister Gesang,
I promised the Master
not to tell anyone about this.
Plus,
I am
tight-lipped.
So stop asking me about it.
So you haven't seen it then.
Of course I have!
When he transforms, he glows with golden light,
and holds a five-colored sword.
Pretend I didn't say anything.
I'm leaving.
Then it must be him.
Ping Jie, Qiang Haihui.